First, today we are
presenting a very long term chart of ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company. We will be discussing its results.
Research on the matter.
Good morning. Look at this long
chart. This quarter has been a bit soft.
Weak figures have been presented. Actually, due to
withdrawals, the underwriting office has
increased a lot and
due to this,
look at the profitability figures, the profitability figure has come down from Rs 398 crore to Rs 152 crore
and against a profit of Rs 30 crore, the
underwriting loss has come down to Rs 508 crore
in this quarter. That is why we have seen that
pressure. Actually, look at the profit figures
next month, there is a slight
increase in it. You have seen around Rs 270 crore or
less, but that
underwriting loss has been heavy.
In combined losses also, we have seen that the figure has increased from 102 percent to
121 percent, but the
cost has disappointed. Actually, the concessions are
high in this quarter. In this quarter,
here today, in the same quarter last year, it was Rs 1621
crore.  Claims worth Rs 2468 crore have been seen
going in and due to this, the pressure on
underwriting has increased further, which has put pressure on the
number subscribed on the plate
and the report has come from the back side,
they said that there is definitely a Taliban off in the
scooter, they have
definitely revised the target in the past but it is not very big, the
earlier target was Rs 1575, after
revising it, gold has been tested around Rs 100
and there is an out for sight rating,
they believe that the situation in the second half and share will be
seen to be getting a little better in comparison to this quarter, in the
fourth quarter of guest house,
when we look at the special
underwriting and limited numbers of around Rs 500,
but yes,
they feel that the overall situation will have to get better as soon as
1423 on words, the
replacement for f22 has definitely been removed
around cars paste percent but
for reference 2334, the patient data of only around three to five percent
Overall we are seeing a lot of damage
but we are still at the appointed site
from the target to Bijnor of the rest.